panduit.com 2005-12-18

# Panduit Privacy Policy

Panduit Privacy Policy

Panduit is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following policy to understand how any personal information you provide will be treated. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. Panduit has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the Panduit web site. 

This Statement will let you know: 

**1) What we track**   
**2) What we do with the information we gather**   
**3) Cookie Disclosure Statement**   
**4) How to Contact Panduit**   
**1) What we track**  
Our site's registration forms require you to give us contact information (like your first name, last name, and email address), demographic information (like your zip code), and your professional interest information (like industry and profession). Panduit retains this information for our internal use only. 

Our site uses cookies to keep track of your visits to www.panduit.com. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests each time you visit our site. While these activities depend on the use of a cookie, visitors to the Panduit web site always have the option of disabling cookies via their browser preferences. 

Panduit also collects IP addresses for system administration and to report aggregate information on users to the site. 

**2) What we do with the information we gather**  
We use the information you provide only for our internal use: we never sell or share the information you provide with any third parties.

We are continually striving to make the Panduit web site a better information site for you. In order to do that, we continually monitor and analyze the aggregate information we collect on our users. We analyze traffic patterns throughout the Panduit site to highlight popular areas, and improve the sections which are not meeting the needs of our users. 

We may occasionally use customer contact information and professional interest information from the registration form to send email announcements about our new products, etc and to contact you if there are any changes to the site that will affect your user experience. 

**3) Cookie Disclosure Statement**   
**What's A Cookie?**  
A cookie is a small file that's sent to your computer by a site's server. A cookie can be a record of your visit to a site, including information such as your user name, time of last visit, pages viewed, etc. Cookies cannot get information from your hard drive against your will, destroy files, send you viruses, etc. Cookies also allow sites to track aggregate -- not individual -- page views, which helps us develop new features and services that our viewers are interested in. 

The cookie is a text file containing information that allows sites to save your personal settings. Be assured cookies do not breach your privacy. Moreover, they save you time by remembering your personalized settings. 

**So What's In It For You?**  
Here's a quick rundown of what we see as the biggest advantages of cookies: 

• Faster, more secure access: So we don't have to ask you to identify yourself with each new page requested.   
• We can deliver you customized information and store your settings more efficiently.   
• Better information: We want to give you features and services that you're interested in. By monitoring popular -- and not-so-popular -- features in an aggregate manner, we can better serve your needs.   

**To change your cookies click _here_ to see instructions on how to modify your browser’s cookie settings.**

**4) Our contact information**   
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your experiences with this web site, you can contact Panduit at: 

Panduit Corp.   
17301 South Ridgeland Avenue   
Tinley Park, Illinois 60477   
800-777-3300 Ext 1599 

_[Ask A Question](http://panduit.custhelp.com/cgi-bin/panduit.cfg/php/enduser/ask.php)_
